(Howard:)C-6 was a hit, C-8 was a hit.
(Howard:)Part of your starship
has to be on C-7.
(Raj:)Not if it has a hole
in the middle.
(Howard:)What kind of spaceship
has a hole in the middle?
(Raj:)A Romulan Battle Bagel?
(Bernadette:)Knock-knock.
(Howard:)Oh, great, you made it.
(Penny's Dad:)Come on in.
(Howard:)I invited her.
(Bernadette:)So where's
the telescope?
(Howard:)It's in Hawaii, but Raj
controls it from here.
(Howard:)He's hoping to see Epsilon
Eridani dim, which would be
(Howard:)evidence of a planet
orbiting it.
(Bernadette:)So we just sit and stare
at the screen,
(Bernadette:)waiting for
something to happen?
I did it with you when
we rented The Notebook.
(Howard:)Yes, Gena Rowlands
is a treasure.
(Howard:)You'd better open up
that bottle of wine
(Howard:)or I'm gonna end up
with swimmer's ear.
(Raj:)Excuse me.
(Raj:)I can't be drinking,
I'm about to make
(Raj:)an important scientific
discovery here.
(Howard:)What? Galileo did his best work
while drinking wine.